modifiedcars.com 2012-02-17

# ModifiedCars.com » Privacy Policy

---|---  
  
  * It is modifiedcars.com's policy that personal information, such as your name, postal and e-mail address or telephone number, is private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you provide is accessible only by designated staff, and is used only for the purposes for which you provide the information (such as to reply to your request or enquiry).
  * Personal information will not be released to third parties. except if release is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings. There are no other circumstances under which we will provide or sell personal information to third parties.
  * This site makes use of forums available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
  * This site, modifiedcars.com, uses the services of Fastclick, Tribual Fusion for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, the agencies collects anonymous data through the use of cookies.
  * We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

##  Terms and Conditions

  * By accessing this website you agree that modifiedcars.com shall not be liable to any person for any loss or damage which may arise from the use of any of the information contained in any of the materials on this website.
  * Hypertext links in this website will lead to websites which are not under the control of modifiedcars.com. Third party links are included solely for your convenience and do not constitute any endorsement by modifiedcars.com of third party products or services. When you activate these you will leave the modifiedcars.com website and modifiedcars.com has no control over and will accept no liability in respect of the material on any website which is not under the control of modifiedcars.com.
  * The information contained on this website is for information purposes. Whilst every care has been taken in its preparation, modifiedcars.com does not make any warranties nor representations as to its accuracy or reliability. We neither accept nor assume any reliability in relation to the contents of these pages which should not be relied upon as accurate. In no event do we accept liability of any description including liability for negligence for any damages whatsoever resulting from loss of use, data or profits arising out of or in connection with the viewing, use or performance of this website or its contents.
  * modifiedcars.com assumes no responsibility for and disclaims all liability for any errors or omissions, which may be referred to or linked to by this site.
  * All product names mentioned herein are the trademarks of their respective owners.
  * The pages contained in this website may contain technical inaccuracies and typographical errors. The information in these pages may be updated from time to time and may at times be out of date. We accept neither responsibility for keeping the information in these pages up to date nor liability for any failure to do so.
  * You and any user of your Account must evaluate, and bear the risk associated with, the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of any Content. modifiedcars.com shall not be responsible for any Content. modifiedcars.com does not prescreen or monitor all Content as a matter of policy, but modifiedcars.com shall have the right, but not the responsibility, to remove Content which is deemed in modifiedcars.com's sole discretion harmful, offensive, or otherwise in violation of this Agreement or any rules modifiedcars.com has in place at the time.
  * Information contained on the modifiedcars.com website listed has not been independently verified by modifiedcars.com.
  * modifiedcars.com does not and cannot review all materials posted to the modifiedcars.com Web Site by users, and modifiedcars.com is not responsible for any such materials posted by users. However, modifiedcars.com reserves the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation or government request, or to edit, refuse to post or to remove any information or materials, in whole or in part, that in modifiedcars.com's sole discretion are objectionable or in violation of this Agreement.
  * We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.
